playdo.com 2008-06-13

# Privacy Policy

You can trust us at Playdo. We swear solely that we will protect and keep your personal information private and never share it with other companies or other people without your permission. As long as you don't break any of the rules (described in the terms and conditions) and laws (local, national or international), your privacy is safe with Playdo; If you do however, we might have to share your information with Legal Authorities.

The information we collect about you helps us to serve you better and allows us to get in touch with you. 

You will be notified about how all information you give us will be used and if, or how, it'll be displayed in Playdo. Some information is public so people can communicate with you and the rest is private or set in different levels of privacy. 

NEVER share any personal information - in chat rooms, blogs, guest books or your profile - if you are not TOTALLY sure and aware of that you want to show it to the world. This is your very own responsibility, don't take lightly on this. Playdo reserves the right to, but do not promise to, temporarily hide personal information posted by you while checking with you (or your parents if you are under 18) that it is really OK.

 **Posted Content:**

The content you post in Playdo is stored into our database and it is part of Playdo content. However, Playdo will not publish or take it outside the Playdo Services and products without the user's consent. Playdo reserves the right to delete inappropriate content or forward any illegal content to third parties and law enforcement. 

**E-mail:**

We may from time to time e-mail you with informative messages about services or third party products and services we believe you might be interested in. 

The newsletters may contain codes that enable our database to track your usage of the newsletters, including if the email was opened and/or what links (if any) were clicked. We can combine that information with other information we have about you to improve your site experience and/or provide customized communication to you. 

**Chat:**

The chat is monitored by authorized personal in order to maintain it a friendly and cheerful place. Whisper and private messages might be monitored by administrators although the content remains private. See the Chat Codes of Conduct for more information. 

**Password:**

Your password is the master key to your profile. So try to use a password that is hard to guess. And even though it might sound a bit obvious, we must remind you not to give it to anyone. We will NEVER ask you for your password so don't be fooled by e-mails that do so. 

**Security measures:**

Playdo keeps logs of chat conversations and messages sent in order to keep the environment safe and cheerful, which means free of bad language, sexual, violent and illegal content and suitable for users of all ages. **** Logs and user's information are confidential and not shared with any third parties except when requested by law enforcement.

As a security measure, Playdo reserves the right to have its moderators and staff members to read and monitor "whispers" and private messages although the content remains private, unless when requested to be disclosed by law enforcement agencies in the case of a crime investigation.

When a parent agrees with the registration of a child under 13, he or she also states that has read, understood and agree with these Terms and Conditions of usage. 

**IP Address:**

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a unique string of numbers, like a bar code or an ID, that your server and Internet Provider give to your computer. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. IP addresses are used only to help us find and fix problems with our server and to administer the site and to contact you. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information. But again, we will never share your IP address with anyone else. It's our little secret! 

**If you have any further questions about Playdo's Privacy Policy, please don't hesitate to contact us throughSupport.**

Last update: February 20th, 2008

© 1999-2008 Playdo. All rights reserved.   
Parts of this site contain the copyrighted content of members and other third parties.   
Title to this content and related rights are reserved by the respective copyright owner.
